# **TUMEKA BURSTON**

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

#### **DETAILS**

#### PHONE

07805028631

#### **EMAIL**

burston1993@icloud.com

#### LINKS

GitHub

<u>LinkedIn</u>

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5 & CSS

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

JavaScript

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

Git

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

React

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

Laravel

• • • 0 0

PHP

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

Fiama

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

# HOBBIES

Kickboxing: Graded at a local club
Twitter: Run an Animal
Crossing account and
contribute to the
community regularly
Skillshare: Take short online
courses for personal and
professional development

#### **PROFILE**

A fresh full-stack developer based in Bristol, UK, focused mainly on front-end development, with knowledge and experience in server-side programming. Previously worked in Hospitality, Retail and in Offices over the last 8 years, whilst consistently demonstrating the ability to adapt to new environments and challenges. A strong worker skilled in team-work, team leadership, Communication, Problem Solving with user-friendly solutions and detail-orientated.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Full Stack Software Development, DevelopMe\_

Bristol, UK (Remote)

Sep 2020 — Dec 2020

Intensive project-driven 12 week software development on the webstack course, taught by industry professionals using best practice approaches.

# **Professional Musicianship, University of Bristol**

Bristol, UK

Sep 2013 — Jul 2016

A 3 year degree course learning business models, live sound engineering, working with and managing people, live performance best practices and theory concepts. Final Year Project (Dissertation): Composing music and Sound Design to Video Games. 2:1 was achieved on this degree.

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

# City of Bristol College, Bristol - HE & Quality Administrator, City of Bristol College

Bristol, UK

Sep 2019 — Aug 2020

Worked collaboratively across college, engaging in **implementing changes** and **promoting innovation** whilst supporting and providing oversight of daily tasks and legacy projects.

## **Assistant Store Manager, Game Ltd**

Bristol, UK

Apr 2017 — Jul 2019

Supervised and managed one of Britain's largest GAME stores whilst consistently improving the store's KPI by being **goal-orientated**, **strategic in planning** and **commercial awareness.** 

### Bar Manager, Stowford Meadows Farm

Barnstaple, Devon

Mar 2013 — Oct 2016

**Effectively** oversaw a large Bar at a busy holiday caravan site, whilst being **resourceful, calm** in high stress scenarios and able to **delegate duties** with respect.